Hello friends, welcome to our
[music]. This
seems like a perfect setup.
If we plan for it, as
it has broken through this candle,
if it retests this zone in the coming days, then there could be an
opportunity for us.
We
can place a stop loss below this candle.
Otherwise, if it breaks this range, it will become even
stronger.
It is going to break out of a very good consolidation.
If it reaches this zone, it has been almost
86 days. So,
I think if the breakout sustains, then
a good move can be seen from here.
But the market situation is quite tough, so we
need to work very carefully here. Here, the first priority
for a trader should be to
protect his capital. Right now, there is no bull run, that
you will work in any breakout stock
and if the breakout sustains and
some returns will be generated from there, then I am
convinced that if a positive candle is
formed here, then I will look to make an entry,
otherwise I will wait. If this level is also
good,  It breaks with a candle,
in the coming few days it consolidates and breaks with a
good candle with good volume,
then in this we
can see its all time high, its
target, but it is a big company, so
fast moves do not come that quickly,
if seen from here,
this range of
ours at 12,
it will also take a lot of time to give a move, so
work with great caution, okay, you will get a lot of trades when the
market situation improves, right now
just practice, learn,
look at the charts
and it is better to maintain some distance from the market
because the market situation is
very bad, the selling of AE has not stopped
and until their buying comes, it
is very difficult for Nifty to move, if Nifty does
not move
then the condition of particular stock will remain the same, I hope
you all liked this video, if you liked the
video informative
then give lots of love, we will meet
in the next video, thanks for watching this
video, Jai Hind, Jai Bharat, Vande Mataram
friends